take your photography to new heights
with the pintx kx
a compact user-friendly digital slr with
impressively advanced features
at an attractive price
the kx's high resolution 12.4 megapixel
cmos
image sensor offers superior image
resolution with maximum control over
noise
and supports live view the pintx
original shake reduction system
stabilizes image and video giving up to
four stops of compensation for stunning
blur free pictures and movies
best of all it's compatible with every
pentax lens
ever produced many powerful scene modes
let you choose the perfect settings for
any situation while helping new
photographers learn digital slr
photography
or let auto picture mode do all of the
work for you
the fast responsive 11 point wide angle
autofocus system
focuses quickly and accurately even with
moving subjects
and expanded iso range improves
performance in extreme low light
conditions
the pintx prime2 image processing engine
captures up to 4.7 frames per second
with a top shutter speed of one six
thousandth of a second
fast circuitry and low noise image
processing make it ideal for sporting
events
or any fast action situation you can
even capture
full seven twenty p widescreen hd video
on the pentax kx at 24 frames per second
and record sound using the built-in
microphone